Hello friends,
welcome to the Shraddha club. Friends, at this time
on the daily chart of ICICI Lombard stock,
you can see that it is a good one. Here, by
changing its trend, the stock is turning upwards.
Based on this, the stock has shown such a big trend here,
but after going up,
once this channel pattern has formed here,
we call it Barrister Army Canteen
pattern and after this pattern is formed,
we have got the confirmation channel here
which was formed today and the
confirmation candle has given
its closing below the low of our channel like pattern, that is,
if you will see, the
low of this candlestick pattern is
more than 100. Today our low is
more than 150. We have got this confirmation on the date below it.
If you have a
holding in stock, then you can book your profit
or else you can start trailing your stop loss here,
that if it goes
down further, then you are making profit
and you have to decide to lose more here, so
friends, if you
take any stock, then you can book your profit yourself.  Analyze
and see whether the spread is
appearing in your recent report or not, if it is
not appearing in your research report then
ignore that share there,
leave this spread here, friends, that is why I do
not keep it, if you have
any doubt related to the topic then definitely ask by commenting,
if you have not subscribed to my channel yet,
subscribe immediately, will
meet you soon with the cut in the new video
[Music]